两张黑桃
Two spades.
三张红心
Three hearts.
都是你的了
It's all yours.
我放弃
I fold.
这里有5张
And that's five.
这里有6张
And that's six.
耶!不算太坏
Yay!,Not bad.
根据满贯的规矩,通常情况下你要,尽快让赢家赢
On a slam contract, you normally,want to play your winners early.
对不起,爸爸
Sorry, Dad.
不.你正在学习呢,你做的很好
Nah. You're learning.,You're doing fine.
Connie Gilman是一个好选手
Connie Gilman's a good player.
也是个活寡妇
And a widow.
我应该,呃,把她带出来
I should, uh, take her out
因为她会玩桥牌
because she can play bridge.
你真的很会想像
You're a true romantic.
你应该叫某人出来
You should ask somebody out.
你觉得Cecile还没有约会过吗?
You think Cecile's,not dating yet?
Cecile在她离开之前正在约会
Cecile was dating,before she left.
哦,闭嘴,Marv
Oh, shut up, Marv.
不.我有个好伙伴
No. I have a partner.
她做的非常好
And she's doing great.
Amy应该出来找找乐子
Amy should be out,having fun.
我很开心
I'm having fun.
是啊
Yeah.
看来你正在享受你的生命
Look like you're having,the time of your life.
无将约定(桥牌中的一种规则)
One no trump.
我有一些...恶心
I'm just...a little nauseous.
我,呃,我想我是吃的太多了
I, uh, I think I ate too much.
我们能休息一下吗?
Can we take a break?
当然
Of course.
不好意思
Excuse us.
你吃了什么?
What did you eat?
没什么乱七八糟的
Nothing weird.
- 你喝酒了吗?,- 没有,爸爸.你知道我不-
Have you been drinking?,No, Dad.,You know I don't--
因为我不介意你是否--
Because I don't mind if you--
爸爸?
Dad?
[echoing],Dad?
爸爸,你在做什么?
Dad, what are you doing?
你吓到我了.很疼
You're scaring me. It hurts.
放手!你在做什么?
Let go!,What are you doing?
Henry?
,Henry?
Henry
Henry.
放开她
Let go of her.
偶尔喝点酒
The occasional drink
对我来说并没什么
doesn't bother me.
但是...
But...
怎么了?
What?
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
怎么了?
What's the matter?
你得了一种叫做"失神发作"的病
You had what's called,an "absence seizure."
你之前有过类似的症状吗?
Anything like that,happen to you before?
不,没有
No, Nothing.
他真的很健康
He's been really healthy.
他出去散步,吃的很正常.他--
He jogs, he eats right.,He--
我--我上个星期天有些头疼
I--well, I did have a headache,last Sunday.
过去两年,我一直
And for the past two years,,I've been getting
在反胃酸
acid reflux a lot.
我觉得,呃,我所需要的只是抗酸药物
And I thought that, uh, antacids,were all I needed.
我应该早一些过来吗?
Should I have come in sooner?
就因为反胃酸和头疼?
For acid reflux and a headache?
嗯,我--你知道,我听说楼下的咖啡
Well, I--you know, I hear,the coffee downstairs
味道很不错
is really good.
你能帮我去买一杯吗,亲爱的?
Could you get me a cup, Honey?
你介意把百叶窗关上吗?
Would you mind,closing the blinds?
他右边的睾丸几乎有他左边的两倍那么大
,His right testicle is almost,twice as big as his left.
酷
Cool.
可能是睾丸癌
It's probably,testicular cancer.
嗯,不是
,Mmm, no.
那是不可能的
That's impossible.
所有显示出来的症状--
The symptoms all indicate--
鞋子不对
The shoes aren't right.
睾丸癌可以这么自己来证明
Here's how testicular cancer,would manifest itself.
首先,病人会说出他自己
First, the patient would get,the exact symptoms
准确的症状
that he's got.
然后Foreman会对他进行检查
Then Foreman would examine him.
由于症状是那么明显,然后他就会
Then he'd suspect,testicular cancer on account of
怀疑是睾丸癌
the symptoms being so perfect.
然后他会往里面戳根针,再打电话给一个外科医生
Then he'd stick a needle in it.,Then he'd call a surgeon.
在那个家伙做手术的时候,我们剩下的人
And while that guy operates,,the rest of us
就可以出去打保龄球了
would be out bowling.
既然我们没有穿保龄球的鞋子
And since we're not,wearing bowling shoes,
所以这个病很明显不是这么来处理的
the disease obviously did not,progress in that fashion.
标准腹腔镜手术显示有一些白色的细胞,但他的核磁共振检查什么也没有
LP showed some white cells.,But his MRI is clean.
当然.如果你把他脑袋中的微脓肿叫做"什么也没有"
Sure. If you call a microabscess,in his brain "clean."
什么,你不相信我?
What, you don't trust me?
你是在说左边那个暂时性突出物?
Are you talking about,the left temporal lobe?
太好了.你可以透过我的手看到
Neat.,You can see through my hand.
这只是一个阴影
It's just a shadow.
或者就是一个感染源
Or it's an infection.
当人们有头脑/胯部的毛病
When guys have brain/crotch,problems,
结果通常都是一边使用的太多
it's usually the result of using,one too much
而另一边太少
and the other too little.
血液和尿样的检查
,Blood and urine were negative
都显示梅毒,淋病和衣原体为阴性
for syphilis, gonorrhea,,and chlamydia.
那就以这三种毛病来治疗.马上
So treat him for all three.,Stat.
嗯...阴性就表示他没有得
Um...negative means,he doesn't have it.
不,阴性只表示他可能没有得
No. Negative means,he probably doesn't have it.
表示他可能得了癌症
Which means he probably,has cancer.
我以为我们穿错了治疗癌症的鞋子
I thought we were wearing,the wrong shoes for cancer.
我们穿错了治疗睾丸癌的鞋子
We're wearing the wrong shoes,for testicular cancer.
但对于淋巴瘤来说是正确的,除了Chase
They're perfect for lymphoma.,Except Chase's.
它们真的很蠢
They're just goofy.
淋巴瘤会导致他的生殖器官
Lymphoma could cause infiltrants,in his reproductive organs
和脑子中有浸渍剂
and his brain.
如果到了那个时候,不管我们做什么他都死定了
If it's this advanced,,he's dead no matter what we do.
给他进行性传播疾病测试,希望测试是错的
So give him the STD meds,and hope the tests were wrong.
Svinnuk.谁是那个幸运的女人?
Svinnuk.,Who's the lucky woman?
我妻子
My wife.
不,我不想知道是谁拿到了巧克力
No, I don't want to know,who gets the chocolates.
我想知道你正在和谁乱搞
I want to know who,you're having the affair with.
他在是孩子的时候把脑子撞坏了,真是悲惨
Fell on his head as a child.,Tragic.
挪威巧克力
Norwegian chocolate.
坦白说,你买那个东西,恐怖分子赢了
Frankly, you buy that stuff,,the terrorists win.
有些人会把他们的感觉用瓶子封装起来
Some people bottle up,their feelings,
作为物理疼痛释放出来
have them come out,as physical pain.
健康的人会表达自己的感觉
Healthy human beings,express feelings,
比如爱情,就通过赠送礼物
such as affection,,by giving gifts.
礼物表示有罪恶
Gifts express guilt.
表达得越贵
The more expensive,the expression,
说明罪恶越深
the deeper the guilt.
那只有12美元一盒
That's a $12 box.
所以要么你还没有和她睡觉
So either you haven't,slept with her yet,
要么她并不是那么好
or she wasn't that good.
不是所有的都和性有关,House
It's not all about sex, House.
真的?什么时候变的?
Really?,When did that change?
我想打避孕注射剂
I want to get Depo-Provera.
事实上,在你的年龄
Actually, at your age,
只要你小心一些
as long as you're careful,
你怀孕的风险是非常有限的
the risk of you getting pregnant,is pretty limited.
是的,但它能让我平静下来,是吗?
Yeah, but it would,calm me down. Right?
如果我注射了足够多的剂量
If I get a high enough dose.
你说的"平静"是指某个凉爽的夏季晚上
You mean "calm",as in a peaceful lake,
的平静的湖?
on cool summer evening?
还是我们通常所说的
Or in the lesser used,meaning of,
没有什么可以再打搅你了
nothing can ever,bother you again
因为生命对你来说再没有什么意义
because life has absolutely,no meaning?
高剂量的避孕注射剂
High dose of Depo-Provera
会化学性的阉割你
will chemically castrate you.
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
我现在准备起身离开
I'm gonna get up to leave now.
走到那扇门前,转动把手
And I'm gonna a walk,to that door, turn the handle.
然后你会突然决定
And then you're suddenly,gonna decide
你必须告诉我事实
that you have to,tell me the truth.
而我不得不转身在一路走回来
I'm gonna have to turn around,and come all the way back.
看,问题是,我的腿很疼
See, the thing is,,my leg hurts.
我们能不能就保持现状别让我走动?
Can we cut the walking,out of the equation?
我爱上了母牛
I love cows.
有什么特别的...品种吗?
Any particular...variety?
恩格西奶牛?荷兰乳牛?
Guernseys? Holsteins?
哪种是黑白相间的?
Which are,the black and white ones?
哦,上帝
Oh, God.
我在上学的路上会经过一个农场
I pass a farm,on my way to school.
它们看起来是那么漂亮
And they're so beautiful.
它们是那么的宏伟.我做梦也梦到它们
They're so majestic.,I dream about them.
把它们做成皮鞋,汉堡包
Leather shoes, hamburgers.
有谁可以那么对待一只母牛呢?
How can anybody do that,to a cow?
做爱 而不是做皮带 这很不错
Make love, not belts.,It's beautiful.
- 我实际上并没有--,- 好,放松
I haven't actually--,Well, relax.
作我们医生这行一直在处理这种事情
Something we doctors deal with,all the time.
我会给你写一份药品的名称
I'm gonna write you,the name of a drug.
你并不需要处方
You don't need a prescription.
看起来和注射避孕剂差不多
And it looks,just like Depo-Provera.
但它也能起到相同的作用吗?
But does it do the same thing?
哦,上帝,不
Oh, God, no.
那东西带有所有恶心的副作用
That stuff has all sorts,of nasty side effects.
而这是真正的用药
It's real medicine.
不,这才是你所需要的
No, this is all you need.
你兄弟会的哥们会完全被愚弄
Your frat buddies will be,completely fooled.
告诉他们那个医生是多么的惊骇
Tell them how appalled,the doctor was.
肯定会有很多嘲笑
Lots of laughs.
我们认为你或许有性传播方面的疾病
We think you may have,a sexually transmitted disease.
不,这不可能
No. It's not possible.
先生,或许我们应该私下说一下
Sir, maybe we should,speak in private?
你们给他做了这方面的测试?
Have you tested him for this?
测试显示为阴性
The tests were negative.
那么,就是没有
Well, then it's not that.
那还可能是什么原因呢?
So what else could it be?
没什么好的理由
Nothing good.
如果你曾有过性生活
If you've been having sex,
你必须告诉我
you have to tell me.
自从我离婚后,我就再也没有过性生活
I have not had sex,since my divorce.
我并没有让他吃药
I didn't ask him,to take the medicine.
我是让你给他吃药
I asked you to give him,the medicine.
他已经一年多没有性生活了
He hasn't had sex,in over a year.
- 他在撒谎,- 他知道危险性
He's lying.,He knows wt's at stake.
我们应该马上开始对他进行,淋巴瘤的治疗
We should start treating him,for lymphoma right away.
- 或许如果我们快速用力的打击他--,- Wilson!
Maybe if we hit him,hard and fast--,Wilson!
你可以过多久无性的生活?
How long can you go,without sex?
你可以过多久不让人讨厌的生活?
How long can you go,without annoying people?
不要这样,我是认真的,一个星期?一个月?
No, seriously.,Week? Month?
我并没有在拈花惹草
I'm not having an affair.
我没有说你是
I didn't say you were.
起码不是在这次谈话中
Not in this conversation.
我们正在讨论一个病人的情况
We're talking about a patient.
人们有控制冲动的能力
People have impulse control.
我们并不需要性生活
We don't need sex.
好吧,并不象空气那样
Well, not like air.
但作为生物学方面的需求,我们肯定需要
But as a biological imperative,,sure we do.
我们会为了两件事情而做蠢事
There's two things,we get stupid for.
金钱和性
Money and sex.
既然金钱不太可能会进入血液...
And since money rarely,enters the bloodstream...
你在问他是否有性生活的时候,他的女儿是否在房间里?
Was his daughter in the room,when you asked if he'd had sex?
我告诉他我们可以私下谈一下
I told him we could,talk privately.
他并不介意她是否在那里
He didn't care,if she was there.
已经是中午了,小女孩会去吃午饭
It's almost noon.,Little girl would go to lunch.
在她出门的时候,你去做下记录
Soon as she's out the door,,you're gonna get paged.
然后告诉我
Then you page me.
你的午饭时间还真早,嗯?
Lunch is early, huh?
嗨
Hi.
我是House医生
I'm Dr. House.
我听说你情愿死掉
I hear you'd rather die,than admit
也不愿意承认你有性生活
you had sex.
对不起.我...我不能告诉我的女儿
I'm sorry.,I...couldn't tell my daughter.
很好.因为她...怎么,有22岁了吗?
Right. 'Cause she's...,what, 22?
我和她妈妈一起睡觉
I slept with her mom.
她可能已经知道有这么回事了
She probably knows,that's happened already.
翻身
Roll over.
我的妻子有了外遇,我原谅了她
My wife had an affair.,I forgave her.
她又有了另一次外遇
She had another affair.
我再一次原谅了她
And I forgave her again.
然后...Amy觉得
And...Amy thinks
我是一个傻瓜
I was an idiot.
挺痛苦的.你一定非常骄傲
So smart.,You must be very proud.
翻身
Roll over.
我假定你是在谈恋爱
I assume you've been in love.
我帮你进行性传染病的鸡尾酒治疗
I'm starting you on a cocktail,of STD meds.
Amy刚刚熬过这段时间
Amy is just getting over it.
她已经好几个月没有和她妈妈说话了
She barely spoke to her mom,for months.
如果她知道又发生了相同的事情
If she thought that,it was happening again,
而且正是我得病的原因--
that that's why I got sick--
我们只是在同一个
We just happened,to be at the same
意大利乳酪品尝会上碰见
Italian cheese-tasting thing.
乳酪是恶魔的玩具
Cheese is the devil's plaything.
就只有一个晚上
It was just the one night.
哦,你很明显完全忘记她了
Oh, you're obviously,completely over her.
Amy觉得爱情会让你作出愚蠢的选择
Amy thinks love leads you,to make stupid choices.
你还正好为她树立了一个好的榜样
You're certainly setting,a good example for her.
她只是还没有领会到
She just doesn't get it.
如果你没有准备好看起来很愚蠢的样子
If you're not prepared,to look stupid,
那就不会发生什么好事,不是吗?
then nothing great is ever,gonna happen, right?
话说回来
On the other hand,
我猜你的睾丸都没有要爆炸的趋势
I guess your testicles aren't,going to explode either.
爸爸
Dad.
没什么事情吧?
Is everything okay?
我得了性传播疾病
I have a sexually transmitted,disease.
怎么可能?
How's that possible?
他在教堂里碰到了一个女人
He met a woman in church.
她玩桥牌吗?
Does she play bridge?
她玩--
[laughing],Does she--
急救车!,哦,上帝...
Crash cart!,Oh, God...
这是另外一种发作吗?
Is this another seizure?
闭嘴
Shut up.
进来!
Comin' in!
哦,上帝
,Oh, God.
40毫克的利尿磺胺
40 milligrams furosemide.
把他打开
Knock him out.
性传染病怎么会这样?
How would an STD do this?
这是瞬间肺部水肿
,It was flash pulmonary edema.
我们取走了一公升的液体
We took a liter of fluid off,
但问题不是他的肺
but the problem wasn't,with his lungs.
是他的心脏
It's his heart.
有赘生物
There are vegetations
阻碍了他的冠状动脉
obstructing his mitral valve.
这不是性传染病
,It's not an STD.
淋巴瘤不会那么突然爆发
Lymphoma wouldn't erupt,that suddenly.
那会是什么?
So what is it, then?
一种攻击他的
A disease that attacks
脑部,心脏和睾丸的疾病
his brain, heart,,and testicles.
我觉得拜伦写过这种毛病
I think Byron wrote about that.
可能是鹦鹉热
Could be psittacosis.
衣原体培养恢复显示为阳性
,Chlamydia cultures would've,come back positive.
绿色霉素链球装菌会伤害到心脏
Strep viridans,can hit the heart.
但不会导致生殖系统的紊乱
Wouldn't mess with,the reproductive system.
或许事情并不是...那么巧妙地关联
Maybe things aren't...,so nicely connected.
他65岁了
He's 65.
我们可以找一下多种系统疾病
We could be looking at,multiple systems
不要只盯着一个独立系统的损坏
just starting to break down,independently.
到达一个男人的心脏
Way to a man's heart
是要通过他的胃
is through his stomach.
他已经好几年反胃酸了
,He's had acid reflux for years.
这-不会有所联系吧
It--it can't be relevant.
看来除了性生活之外
,It seems there are other ways
还有其他的办法会把人杀死
to kill people besides,having sex with them.
你不是那么需要这个
You don't need this so much.
问题不是你的肺
Problem is not your lungs.
是你的心脏
It's your heart.
那个教堂里的意大利干酪
That Italian cheese thing,at the church.
是什么样的干酪?
What sort of cheese?
你为什么需要知道?
Why do you need to know?
我要去参加一个干酪聚会
I'm having a fondue party.
是羊的干酪吗?
Was it sheep cheese?
可能是.为什么这么问?
Might have been.,Why?
很软吗?
Was it soft?
是的
Yeah.
吃起来象粪便一样?
Taste like crap?
是啊.很难吃
Yeah. Bitter.
吃起来象这个?
Taste like this?
是啊.但怎么--
Yeah. But how did--
那是美国人一般吃的低脂的
That was regular,low-fat American.
我加了一些细菌
I added some bacteria.
作为调味
For flavor.
你给他喂细菌?
You fed him bacteria?
几乎所有的东西上都有
It's pretty much,on everything.
特别是未经高温消毒的羊干酪
Especially the unpasteurized,sheep cheese
他们在阿尔卑斯山制作
they make in the Alps.
那东西会带给你普鲁氏菌病
That stuff will give you,brucellosis.
长命的关键.异国女子,讨厌的干酪
Key to a long life.,Exotic women, boring cheese.
会对你进行利福平
Gonna start you on rifampin
和强力霉素治疗
and doxycycline.
可没什么意义啊
Doesn't make any sense.
我是说,教堂里的其他人都没有生病
I mean, nobody else,at the church got sick.
99.9%的基督徒
99.9 percent of Christians
在胃里面有许多的胃酸
have so much acid,in their stomach,
它们会变成熔化干酪的锅炉
they become churning cauldrons,of death
使得那些恶心的普鲁氏菌死掉
for all those nasty little,brucellosis bugs.
但由于你一直反胃酸而在使用抗酸剂
But you were taking antacids,for your acid reflux.
所以就使得你的消化管道
So that turns,your digestive tract
变成了所有那些
into a pleasant scenic river
病菌舒适的温床
for all those,bacterial tourists.
- 你确信你是正确的?,- 绝对
You sure you're right?,Absolutely.
你的袜子不匹配
Your socks don't match.
那就表示你是在黑暗中
Which means you got up
起床穿衣的
and got dressed in the dark,
也就表示你不想吵醒你的妻子
which means you don't want,to wake your wife.
也表示你不想和她说话
Which means you don't want,to talk to her.
还说明--
Which means--
我是在说你的病人
I was referring to your patient.
哦,那个,不
Oh, that. No.
拜托,我是根据干酪来医治的
Come on, I'm basing it,on cheese.
还要多久才能拿到测试结果?
How long before,you get the tests back?
我们会在拿到之前就知道结果了
We'll know before that.
如果我错了,他的病情会继续恶化,然后慢慢死亡
If I'm wrong, he'll just keep,getting worse and slowly die.
但如果我是对的,那我们都能够节约时间
But if I'm right,,either we caught it in time
他也会慢慢好起来
and he gets better.
也可能我们会更忙而他
Or we didn't and he goes
会在某个时刻需要用到强心剂
into cardiac arrest,at any moment.
电击器
Paddles.
充电
Charging.
250.开始
250. Clear.
充电.300
Charging. 300.
开始
Clear.
充电.360.开始
Charging. 360. Clear.
注射肾上腺素
Epinephrine.
你要告诉她吗?
Are you gonna tell her?
说你怀疑我有外遇?,当然
That you suspect an affair?,Sure.
她已经很讨厌你了,为什么不告诉她呢?
Well, she already hates you,,why not?
因为你觉得把这件事情说出来
Because you think,that getting it off your chest
会让你晚上睡得更好一些
will let you sleep better.
不会的
It won't.
你会在我粗笨的睡椅上醒过来
You'll end up sleeping,on my lumpy couch.
没什么可说的
There's nothing to tell.
那为什么你会在晚上8点的时候还在这里玩足球?
Then why are you playing,foosball here at 8:00 at night?
你总是要去简化所有的事情
You always want,to simplify everything.
说好听的,简单的平衡
[pager beeping],Boil it down to nice,,easy equations.
很好,简单的回答
Nice, easy answers.
回家和你老婆去做爱吧
Go home and have sex,with your wife.
他的心脏回到正常窦性心律
His heart is back,in sinus rhythm.
但受到了极大的损害
There's a lot of damage,,though.
的确是普鲁氏菌病,但我们知道的太晚了
It was brucellosis,,but we got to it too late.
赘生物打破了他的冠动脉
The vegetation broke off,in his main coronary artery
引起了梗塞
and caused an infarction.
他的心肌有一半已经坏死
His heart muscle's,half-dead.
幸运的话他还能活一个礼拜
He'll be lucky,to last a week.
除了这些,他怎么样?
Other than that,,how's he doing?
我是认真的
Seriously.
他的脑,睾丸,肺,扁桃体
His brain, testicle, lungs,,tonsils.
所有这些其他器官怎么样?
How's all that,other stuff doing?
呃...他的脑部现在很好
Uh...his brain is clear now.
泌尿生殖器管道也很好
And so is,the genito-urinary tract.
肾功能也不错
And his kidney function is good.
那么,他所需要的就是一个心脏,他自己的已经没有了
So, all he needs is a heart,,and he's outta here.
他是移植器官名单上的主要候选人
,He's a prime candidate,for transplant.
他不抽烟,适度喝点酒
He doesn't smoke,,drinks moderately.
他的血毒理分析显示为阴性
His tox screen was negative,for illegal drugs.
是合法的
And legal ones.
血液培养监测显示已经完全
Surveillance blood cultures,show absolutely no sign
没有任何普鲁氏菌的存在
of any lingering brucella,bacteria.
他66岁了
He's 66 years old.
他告诉我他65岁,大话王
He told me he was 65.,Liar.
我不管了
I'm outta here.
病人的年龄和手术成功几率
There is an inverse correlation
是成反比的
between patient age,and success rates.
他非常健康
He's in excellent health.
在他23岁那年跌断腿以后
This was his first,hospitalization
这可是他第一次住院治疗
since breaking his leg at 23.
可能是22岁.我不太确定了
Or 22.,I'm not sure anymore.
如果这个病人能从手术中存活下来
If this patient were to survive,the operation,
他还能获得什么?
he'd get another what?
5年,10年,或许20年,如果他幸运的话
5, 10, maybe 20 years,if he's very lucky.
所以你是说
,So you're saying
老人不值得和一个年轻人一样来拯救
that old people aren't as worth,saving as young people.
他是说心脏
,He's saying that hearts
是很奇缺的资源
are a scarce resource.
很明显我们必须选择标准--
We obviously have to,choose criteria--
不,我懂了
,No, I get it.
女人能活的更长,所以她们应该有优先权,是吗?
Women live longer, so they,should get preference, right?
而非洲裔美国人
And African-Americans,
他们会死的比较早
they die a lot younger.
所以他们比较该死
So to hell with them.
什么,你觉得你把我称为种族主义者
What, you think,you're gonna win me over
就能说过我吗?
by calling me a racist?
如果测试是说谁应该能活的更长一些
If the test is who gets,to use it the longest,
你可以成为一个种族主义者或者伪君子
you can either be a racist,or a hypocrite.
你的病人有自己的生活,有自己的家庭
Your patient had a life.,A family.
我们有一个18岁的孩子都没有--
We've got 18-year-old kids,who will neve--
你多大了,医生?
How old are you, Doctor?
我们什么时候可以把你扔到冰河里去?
When do we get to toss you,on an ice flow?
好吧,谢谢你,House医生
,And thank you, Dr. House.
如果没有人有其他更多的问题
Unless anybody else,has any further questions,
我们现在要进入私下谈话部分
we will now go,into private session.
哦,我真是坐立不安啊
Oh, I'm on pins and needles.
我非常想知道你们是怎么决定的
I wonder how you'll decide.
网队在赛季中赢得了第三场的胜利
The Nets just won,their third game in a row.
狠狠打击了湖人队
Beat the Lakers.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他们投了否决票
They voted no.
所以...
So...
什么时候...
when...
我会死?
will I die?
或许在一周之内
Might have a week.
我写了一封信给董事会成员
I wrote a letter,to the board of directors,
恳求考虑移植委员会的决定
appealing the transplant,committee's decision.
我说对你的偏见阻碍了他们的医学判断
I'm alleging bias against you,clouded their medical judgment.
我需要你的签名
I need you to sign.
他们已经打了电话
They made the right call.
你并不相信
You don't believe that.
你告诉委员会--
You told the committee--
我是在替我的病人说情
I was advocating,for my patient.
那你为什么--
Then why are you--
帮病人说情
Advocating for my patient.
我门诊的时间到了
I've got clinic duty.
我需要你帮我准备
I need you to get me the files
每个今天死在这里的人的档案
on everybody,who dies here today.
你真的以为这事能改变他们的决定?
You really think this thing'll,change their decision?
不
Nope.
我想我把我的脚踝弄断了
I think I broke my ankle.
我被踢到了,被一只蹄子
I was kicked.,By a hoof.
我沉浸在爱情之中.它是那么的美丽
I'm so in love.,She was so beautiful.
哪个?
Which one?
黑白相间的其中一只
One of the black and white ones.
我并不确定是哪种类型,哪种类型?
I'm not sure what type.,Which "type"?
哪个?我要知道名字
Which one?,I want a name.
为什么它要有名字?,不是"它"
Why would it have a name?,Well, not "it."
是她,或者是他
She. Or he.
我想知道她的梦想,她的希望
I want to know her dreams,,her hopes.
它只是只母牛
It's a cow.
嘿,我可不那个说他沉浸在爱河中的人
Hey, I'm not the one,who said he was in love.
人们真的要将这种情况
People who actually,have this condition
合理化
rationalize it.
他们会不去考虑
They dismiss it.
他们不会将这个提升到诗情画意的地步
They don't elevate it,to the level of poetry.
再加上那里还有块木头碎片
Plus there's a wooden splinter,in there.
所以要么是你自己撞到了一块宽4寸厚2尺的木头
So either you hit yourself,with a two-by-four
要么就是Elsie有一条木头腿
or Elsie has a peg leg.
我6点下班
I'm off duty at 6:00.
要么你自己再去弄自己一下
Give yourself another whack,
回来再编个故事唬其他人吧
come back and scam,somebody else.
我病了
I'm sick.
而你是个医生
And you're a doctor.
你有责任要帮助我
You have a duty to help me.
技术上来说我并不一定要治疗任何人
Technically I don't,have to treat anybody.
除非已经经过一系列
Before running a series
疼痛以及经常性的羞辱性测试后
of painful and often,humiliating tests.
随便你需要什么
Whatever you need.
90岁的女人死于肺炎
90-year-old woman,died of pneumonia.
除非她有一颗超人心脏,下一个呢?
Unless she has a bionic heart,,what's next?
嗯,重症室死了个婴儿
Um...baby died in the ICU.
婴儿没用
Babies are useless.
他们只能得到一颗乒乓球大小的心脏.下一个?
They've got hearts the size,of ping-pong balls. Next?
嗯...40岁的男性...
Um...40-year-old male...
然后?
Yes?
死于心脏病
Heart attack.
如果你真的关心我,你会帮我找到一具更好的尸体
If you really cared about me,,you'd find me a better corpse.
没有其他的死亡病人了
There's no other deaths.
有一个女人遇到了车祸
There's one woman,who was in a car accident.
我希望不太好
Bad one, I hope.
器官获取人员已经都被通知到了
The organ procurement people,have been notified.
把她的档案给我
Give me her file.
在急救室里
It's in the ER.
他们还在对她进行抢救
They're still working on her.
年龄?
Age?
大约40岁
About 40.
很年轻,妈的
Young. Damn.
年轻很好
Young is good.
抽烟吗?
Smoker?
不知道
Don't know.
查一下
Find out.
她还活着
She's still alive.
即使我们被列在名单上
Even if we get on the list,
我们也不能靠近她直到--
we can't go near her until--
超重吗?
Overweight?
属于比较重的类型
She's on the hefty side.
太好了
Excellent.
我们的机会来了
Our odds just went up.
什么机会?
What odds?
这是什么意思?
What is this?
60%捐赠人的心脏会变成
60 percent of potential,donor hearts get tossed
无用的废物,因为其中有问题
in the trash because there's,something wrong with them.
对于胖子来说,几率到达80%
With fat people,,it's closer to 80.
但如果她的心脏不好,那么--
But if her heart's,no good, then--
大,肥,肥大的心脏
Big, fat, sloppy heart.
根本不会好好跳动
Beats no heart at all.
你是Neuberger先生吗?
Are you Mr. Neuberger?
是的
Yes.
我是House医生
I'm Dr. House.
需要问你一些关于你妻子的问题
Need to ask you a few questions,about your wife.
她会好起来吗?
Is she gonna be okay?
我恐怕不能回答你
I'm afraid I don't know that.
你能告诉我关于她的事故吗?
Could you tell me,about her accident?
他们,呃,认为她是睡着了,开出了路中央
They, uh, think she fell asleep,,went off the road.
他们是那么告诉我的
That's all they told me.
到目前为止,她的健康有什么问题吗?
Any problems with her health,up until now?
为什么这么问?
Why?
拜托,这很重要
Please, it's important.
嗯...
Um...
她今天在发烧,否则她也不会--
she had a fever today,,but otherwise she was--
发到多少度?
How high?
大概101度
About 101.
这么多年来她从来没有错过一天的上课
She hasn't missed a day,of teaching in years.
我应该让她待在家里的
And I should've,made her stay home.
还有什么其他症状吗?
Any other symptoms?
有点胃疼吧
A stomachache.
谁管呢
Who cares?
她已经被车撞了
She was in a car crash.
Neuberger先生,是的
,Mr. Neuberger.,Yeah.
我叫Ellen Stambler
My name's Ellen Stambler.
我是南新泽西州的器官
I'm the organ procurement,coordinator
获取协调员
for Southern New Jersey.
我只能对你保证
I just want to assure you
我们会好好的且很尊敬
that we'll treat her organs,with care
的对待她的器官
and dignity.
她的器官?
Her organs?
Laura死了?
Laura died?
我--对不起.,我以为,嗯--
I--I'm sorry.,I thought, um--
她刚刚被宣布死亡
She was just pronounced dead.
我以为她告诉过你
I thought he was telling you.
我不知道
I didn't know.
你永远也不要妄加猜测
You should never,make assumptions.
你想从我这里得到什么?
What did you want from me?
节哀顺变
I'm sorry for your loss.
但我需要你妻子的心脏
???
器官获取协调员
,The organ procurement,coordinator
刚刚离开医院
just left the hospital.
意味着我们运气来了
Means we got lucky.
不管她是否只是去吃午饭
Either that,or she's getting lunch.
死去的女人的姓里面
Dead woman's last name
有字母U还是W?
have a "U" or "W"?
你要偷偷进入
,You're hacking into
机密病人档案吗?
a confidential patient file?
你很难回答吗?
Is that a problem for you?
是"U"
It's a "U."
N-E-U
N-E-U.
Berger
Berger.
三分钟前
Three minutes ago,
她的器官正式被宣布
her organs,were officially declared
无效
not viable.
是进行垃圾搜寻的时候了
Time to go dumpster diving.
嘿
Hey.
她有丙型肝炎
She's got hepatitis C.
她的丙氨酸转化酶指数超过了3倍
Her ALTs are three times normal.
在Henry的免疫系统遭破坏的情况下
With Henry's immune system down,
一个被感染的心脏会杀了他
an infected heart,will kill him.
幸运的是,她没有丙型肝炎
Fortunately, she didn't,have hep C.
她的测试显示为阳性
She tested positive.
她的病史说明了另外的情况
Her history says otherwise.
她丈夫告诉我她正在发烧
Her husband told me,she was running a fever
还有胃疼
with stomach pains.
不是丙型肝炎的症状
Not symptomatic of hep C.
嘿,你在干嘛?你在干嘛?
Hey, what are you doing?,What are you doing?
嘿,你在干嘛?
Hey.,What are you doing?
再一次,对不起
Again, sorry.
我们需要谈一谈
But we need to talk.
Neuberger先生
,Mr. Neuberger
有权利让他妻子从呼吸机上下来
has every right to take his wife,off the ventilator.
他的妻子签署过器官捐赠卡
His wife signed,an organ donor card.
她的器官损坏后就没用了
Which became invalid when,her organs were turned down.
我可以用它们!
I can use them!
我只是需要一点时间
I just need some time.
委员会说他们不会拿走她的心脏
Committee says,they won't take her heart.
另外一个委员会说有人
Another committee,says the guy
不能获得心脏
can't have a heart.
这是天堂般的机遇
It's a marriage,made in heaven.
我可以找到一个外科小组来做手术
I can find a surgical team,that can do this.
作为机密试验
Classified as experimental,
不会算进他们的预算
it's not gonna screw,with their numbers.
这是她想要的
This is what she wanted.
不,她想要她的器官去帮助--
No.,She wanted her organs,to help--
她永远也不想在呼吸机上维持生命
She never wanted to be kept,alive on a ventilator.
她不是.她已经死了!
She's not. She's dead!
她没有疼痛.不会觉得遭罪
She's not in pain.,She's not suffering.
我们只是...只是在这里处理她的肉体
It's just her...meat,we're dealing with here.
这是我的妻子
This is my wife.
不再是了
Not anymore.
她应该获得一些尊严.一些尊重
She deserves some respect.,Some dignity.
我尊重生命,是的
I respect the living.,Right.
这就是为什么你让我觉得你是她的医生
That is why you made me think,that you were her doctor.
让我相信
Made me believe that
或许还有希望
maybe there was some hope.
我从来没有说过我是她的医生
I never said that,I was her doctor.
好吧,你没有撒谎
Fine, you didn't lie.
但你真的没有给我任何尊重
But you sure as hell didn't,give me any respect.
我要把她从呼吸机上弄下来,现在
I am taking her,off the machines. Now.
不错的表演
Nicely played.
还没有结束
It's not over.
对不起
Excuse me.
你是Neuberger先生吗?
Are you Mr. Neuberger?
是的,怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
我是Amy Arrington
I'm Amy Arrington.
我要谢谢你
I wanted to thank you.
这个女孩的父亲
,This girl's father
下个星期就要死了,除非他能得到你妻子的心脏
will die by next weekend unless,he gets your wife's heart.
House.你不觉得有一些操纵吗?
House. Don't you think,that's a little manipulative?
不.是绝对的操纵
No.,It's hugely manipulative.
你是个混蛋
You're an ass.
嘿,听着
,Hey. Listen!
你把你的妻子从生命维持机上取下
You take your wife,off life support,
我会在两周之内忘记这件事情
and I'll have forgotten,about this in two weeks.
而这里的Gai,Amy
Gail here, on the other hand--,Amy.
不管了
Whatever.
你很恼怒我,很好,我接受
You're mad at me.,Fine, I get that.
那就发泄在我身上,不要发泄在她身上
Take it out on me.,Not on her.
哇哦!
Ooh!
很好
Fine.
你的爸爸可以,呃...拥有她的心脏
Your dad can, uh...,have her heart.
发烧,胃疼
Fever. Stomach pain.
提升了肝脏的酶
Raised liver enzymes.
她生病了
She's sick.
比这更糟
Worse than that.
她死了
She's dead.
我的意见是
My point is,
即使她没有得丙型肝炎
even if it's not hep C,
是其他什么毛病
it's something.
他们拒绝了她作为器官的捐赠人
They turned her down,as a donor
因为如果我们把她的心脏放到某人身体里
because if we put that heart,into someone,
他们都不会活下来
they won't survive.
不管是什么让她生的病都会害死他
Whatever made her sick,will kill him.
是啊.那会是什么毛病?
Yeah. So what is it?
- 酶说明--,- 你要我们给
Enzymes indicate--You want us to do
一个死去的人做特别的诊断?
a differential diagnosis,on a dead person?
我们要把她治好
We're going to cure her.
我们要把死人治好?
We're going to cure death?
很明显
Doubt it.
只是想得到她心脏之外的感染源
Just want to get the infection,out of her heart
在我们把心脏从她身体里取出之前
before we get the heart,out of her.
发烧表示
The fever indicates
- 有感染,- 她可能有肝炎
an infection.-She probably has hep C
以及严重的流感
and a bad case of the flu.
假设一下,就为了好玩吧,问题的答案
Let's assume, just for fun,,that the answer
或许对我们会有很大的帮助
is something,that might be helpful.
发烧和胃疼
Fever and belly pain.
可能是胆囊感染
Could be a gall bladder,infection.
差不多
Like that.
做个核磁共振.马上
Do an MRI. Stat.
你真的不需要待在这里
You really don't need to be here.
我假定,呃,House是一个厉害的医生
I assume, uh, House,is a great doctor.
你为什么要这么假定?
Why would you assume that?
因为,呃,如果你是那么个古怪的家伙
Because, uh, when you're,that big a jerk,
要么你很厉害,要么你只能失业
you're either great,or unemployed.
没有胆囊感染的迹象
No sign of gall bladder infection.
但那里有个肿囊
But there was a cyst.
- 非常肥大,- 丙型肝炎不会导致--
Perfectly round.,Now, hep C wouldn't cause--
问题并不是问你是不是丙型肝炎
The question was never,,is it hep C?
给出的问题是说那并不是丙型肝炎
The question was given,that it's not hep C,
是什么?
what is it?
腺瘤?,不够立体
Adenoma?,Not solid enough.
巨型血管瘤?
Cavernous hemangioma?
周围没有血管
Not vascular enough.
如果她在排便后洗手的时候
What if she was sloppy
被污染了呢?
about washing her hands,after pooping?
呃...,变形虫感染?
Uh...,amoeba infection?
如果变形虫病是从她的肝脏开始发作
If the amebiasis started,in her liver,
然后扩展到她的血液中
then spread to her blood,
那就能解释她所有的症状
that would explain,all her symptoms.
除了为什么会撞碎头骨盖
Except for the crushed skull,
而我还很好奇这只是一起小汽车撞车
but I'm assuming that's,from the car crash.
我会开始给她进行巴龙霉素和氯喹的治疗
Ill start her on paromomycin,and chloroquine.
每种十克
Ten grams each.
那...可是正常剂量的20倍
That's...,20 times the normal dose.
是的.所以我们会破坏她的视网膜,还会损害她的听力
Right. So we'll destroy her,retinas and damage her hearing.
无论谁得到这样的治疗都是非常糟糕的一天
Whoever wants those parts,is having a very bad day.
对于她来说,治疗几个小时后,她会感觉非常好的
Couple hours on the meds,,she'll be feeling great.
我得到了你的报告结果
Got your labs.
你吃几内亚猪吗?
Do you eat guinea pigs?
不
No.
那大颊的鼠类和老鼠呢?
How about hamsters or mice?
人?
Humans?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
- 我有什么问题吗?,- 什么都没有
Is something wrong with me?,Absolutely nothing.
你的血液工作非常正常
Your blood work is perfect.
你得到了很多的维他命和矿物质
You've got lots of vitamins,,minerals.
所有的蛋白质
All kinds of proteins.
包括一些被我称为
Including a little something,I like to call
牛的免疫血清的东西
bovine serum albumin.
是通过吃某些你所说过
Which you get from eating
的动物而得来的
the animals mentioned.
或是母牛
Or cow.
你不是真的崇拜母牛
You don't really worship cows.
所以我不得不想知道,还有什么比
So I have to wonder,,what could be more humiliating
有人叫你的女朋友为母牛,而并没有
than someone calling,your girlfriend a cow
隐含寓意在里面更为羞辱的了
and not being metaphorical?
不错
Nice.
这是我的妈妈
It's my mom.
要么这是一张非常老的照片
Well, either that's,a very old photograph,
要么就是你的继母
or it's your stepmom.
她会穿着比基尼在房子里面走来走去,或穿的更少
She goes around the house,in a bikini. Or less.
我-我不能不一直想到她
I-I can't stop thinking,about her.
我的爸爸在欧洲
My dad's in Europe.
我要去看电视,她要给我做按摩
I'll be watching TV,,she'll give me a massage.
我一个小时都不能走路
I can't walk for an hour.
还是老问题.母牛?
Still. Cows?
她可是我的妈妈!
She's my mother!
继母
Step.
求你了
Please.
我只需要3个月的用药
I just need the medicine,for three months
知道我毕业,然后就能搬出屋子
until I graduate and I move,out of the house.
求你了
Please.
你不会在毕业的时候再得到任何乐趣
You're not gonna have any fun,at graduation.
继续保持好好工作
Keep up the good work.
你的衬衣是烫过的
Your shirt is ironed.
那表示你还没有跟你的妻子说什么
That means you haven't told,your wife anything.
就算你是对的吧
Let's say you're right.
你说我说对了?
You're saying I'm right?
不.假设说
No.Let is saying.
那样说是不是会
Does it occur to you,that maybe
比说"闭上你的嘴"要更深刻些?
there's some deeper guidance,than "keep your mouth shut"?
一个朋友的价值对你来说是否
That maybe a friend might
比油腔滑调要高一些呢?
value concern over glibness?
或许...
That maybe...
或许我该检查一下
Maybe I'm going through,something
我是否真的需要真的讨论一下这件事情?
that I need to have,an actual conversation about?
你是否想过你需要
Does it occur to you
这种类型的一个朋友
that if you need,that kind of a friend,
会让你不至于犯下更深刻的错误
you may have made,some deeper errors.
她的心跳不正常
Her heartbeat's irregular.
像是整体运动功能减退
Looks like global hypokinesis.
停止治疗
Stop the meds.
你放弃了?
You're giving up?
要么是我们错了,她的心脏的确不能使用...
Either we're wrong,and her heart is unusable...
如果我们是对的,就是我们给她的治疗
or right, but the treatment,we had to give her
会让她的心脏不能使用
will make her heart unusable.
对不起.你现在可以拔管子了
I'm sorry.,You can pull the plug now.
帮我再找一具尸体吧
Find me another body.
那个服用避孕药的的胖子看来没那么热切
That fat guy on Ortho service,didn't look so hot.
不!
No!
她还没有准备好
She's not ready.
你今天早上就已经准备好了
You were ready this morning.
她还没有死
She's not done.
她要救那个家伙
????
交替理论?
Alternate theories?
变形虫病是我们最希望的
Amebiasis was our best hope.
但事实是她的心跳恢复到了正常速率
The fact that her heart rate,went back to normal
在我们适时停止了治疗后
when we stopped the meds pretty much
那我们第二个希望呢?
What's our second best hope?
House,可以把听筒放下了
House, put down the wand.
那里没有什么障碍物
There's no obstruction.
或许我们应该进行一下
Maybe we should just
活组织切片检查
biopsy it.
她就像是一台拔了电源的冰箱
She's a fridge,with the power out.
如果我们戳开看里面
We start poking around inside,
蔬菜就都会坏掉
the vegetable goes bad.
不能动
No offense.
我觉得我们没太多选择
I don't see that,we have a lot of choice.
唯一可以找到感染源的方法--
The only way we're gonna find,that infection--
如果不是感染呢?
What if it's not an infection?
毒素可以导致相似的症状
Toxins can cause similar symptoms.
特别是在肝脏受损的情况下
Especially if whatever it is,did liver damage.
她,呃,毒理检验正常
Her, uh, toxin screen was clean.
那些仪器永远也照不出
Those things never cover
任何真正的毒素
for any of the really cool,toxins.
再做一次扫描看看你能想到什么
Run the screen again,for whatever you can think of.
你,让另外一个病人继续活着
You, keep the other patient,alive.
你,去检查一下学校
You, check out the school.
我看来需要
And I seem to need
再去雇个医生
to hire another doctor
来检查她的屋子
to go search her home.
来吧
Come on.
如果她正在服用什么药物
If she was taking,any medications,
我会知道的
I'd know about it.
你的妻子染发吗?
Did your wife dye her hair?
不
No.
她妈妈头发一直没有变白
Her mom never went gray.
她也没有
She didn't either.
那我猜这一定是你的
Guess this must be yours, then.
你能否想起有什么她可能会对你撒谎的?
Can you think of anything else,she might've lied to you about?
有什么毒品是在她嫁给你之后戒掉的?
Any drugs she "gave up",when she married you?
你感觉怎么样,先生?
How are you feeling, sir?
Arrington先生?
Mr. Arrington?
怎么了?
What's going on?
他的心脏没有向脑部提供足够的血液
His heart's not pumping enough,blood to his brain.
我们必须给它一些帮助
We're gonna have to give it,some help.
去把充气囊准备好
Get the balloon ready.
你用这个抽屉?
You use this drawer?
不,是放她的维生素的
,No, that's for her vitamins.
安眠药
Sleeping pills.
她从来不吃安眠药
She never took sleeping pills.
好吧
Okay.
你在减肥?
You on a diet?
不
No.
我猜你从未真正去了解过一个人,是吗?
I guess you never really,know someone, do you?
不错的洞察力
Quite the insight.
关于她的头发她对你撒了谎
She lied to you,about her hair color.
不想你知道她觉得她自己很胖
And didn't want you to know,she thought she was fat.
除非你从来没有对她
Unless you never lied to her
撒过什么大谎
about anything that huge.
否则你就不可能让这些事情自然发展
And then you can probably,let those slide.
减肥药会让她的机能混乱
Diet pills could've,messed her up.
引起生物酶升高,导致腹痛
Raised the live enzymes,and caused the bellyache.
但不会发烧
But not the fever.
或许是其他东西导致发烧
Maybe something else,set off the fever.
什么呢?
Like what?
在我给你看这些之前
Before I show you these,
它们是被锁在她书桌的抽屉里
they were in a locked drawer,in her desk.
代校长说肯定是Laura
The vice principal,said that Laura
没收了它们
must've confiscated them.
它们肯定有什么问题--
They've had some problems with--
既不有趣也没有帮助
Neither interesting nor helpful.
至少很有趣
This at least is interesting.
不,不有趣
[No, it's not.
和青少年做爱不有趣吗?
Sex with teenagers,isn't interesting?
你在哪里长大的?
Where did you grow up?
这没什么用
It isn't helpful.
青少年并不是毒素
Teenage boys,aren't toxins.
如果囊肿并不是囊肿呢?
What if the cyst,isn't a cyst?
那我们就没有什么可以再入手了
Then we have nothing to go on.
我说它不是囊肿.没有说它什么都不是
I said it's not a cyst.,I didn't say it was nothing.
如果是一个疮疤呢?
What if it's a scar?
Fitzhugh-Curtis综合症?
Fitzhugh-Curtis syndrome?
你又把它推向淋病的方向?
You're pushing gonorrhea again?
你有什么更好的建议吗?
You got anything better?
对她进行测试
Test her.
对她进行头孢曲松输液治疗
And start her on ceftriaxone.
你们现在在测试什么?
What are you testing for now?
更多的感染
Just some more infections.
她的淋病结果是阳性的
She's positive for gonorrhea.
我觉得这是第一次感到
I think that's the first time,those words
这句话那么让人开心
have been uttered in joy.
开始治疗了
Meds are started.
她的心脏应该在4或5个小时
Her heart should be clear enough,to use
之后就能干净的使用
in about four or five hours.
我去告诉那家人
I'll go tell the families.
他昏迷了
He's in a coma.
给他注射多巴酚丁胺
Start him on dobutamine.
已经注射了
Already did.
我们要么现在就做手术,或者再帮他找个新的脑袋
We either do the surgery now,or we find him a new brain too.
House,她身体系统里还有大量
House, she's still got,a significant amount
的淋病病毒
of gonorrhea in her system.
希望明天它们都会到他的身体里
Hopefully tomorrow,,it'll be in his system.
我需要两个手术室和移植小组
I need two O.R.s,and the transplant team.
怎么了?
What is it?
发生什么事了?
What's going on?
他得到心脏了吗?,是的.对不起
Is he getting a heart?,Yeah.,Excuse me.
我假定这个表示你,呃
assume this means you, uh,
你已经找出Laura有什么毛病了?
you found out,what was wrong with Laura?
她得了变形虫病
She had a amebiasis.
我们刚找到一个别的方法来去除它
We just found a different way,to get rid of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
你可真好
That was kind of you.
我不想让他对我们改变主意
I didn't want him,going postal on us.
一旦他妻子的心脏到了我们手里
Soon as his wife's heart's,in our hands,
你就可以告诉他关于淋病的事情
you can tell him,about the gonorrhea.
他也需要进行测试
He's gotta be tested.
最好在他有下一个性生活之前
Preferably before he gets,any sympathy sex.
电击板
Paddles.
50焦耳
50 joules.
充电
[machines hums to life],Charging.
Charging.
让我们取消他的回路
Let's take him off bypass.
Neuberger先生
Mr. Neuberger.
我必须要告诉你一些事情
There's something,I need to tell you.
去,呃..
The last, uh...
去年左右,呃...
year or so, uh...
Laura对我非常冷淡
Laura was kind of distant,with me.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
我以为或许她有外遇
I thought maybe she was,having an affair.
但...不是Laura的错
But...not Laura.
我并不是为我自己辩解
And I'm not excusing myself,
我在圣诞节旅行的时候
but when I was traveling,during Christmas,
我有了...
I had a...
有了一夜情
I had a one-night stand.
我得了淋病
I got gonorrhea.
你确定--
Are you sure--
是的
Yeah.
我应该告诉你们的
I should've said something,to you.
但我不愿相信是我传染给她的
But I didn't want to believe,that I gave it to her.
让她生病,让她...
That's what made her sick,,and...
才让她出了车祸
that was why she got,into the accident.
Cecile?
我死了吗?
Am I dead?
有希望在很长段时间都不会
Hopefully not,for a long time.
你为什么在这里?
Why are you here?
Amy给我打了电话
Amy called me.
如果你再和妈妈做爱,你必须带上避孕套
If you do Mom again,,you gotta wear a condom.
你的身体里暂时
You're gonna have gonorrhea
带了淋病病毒
in your system for a while.
我能在你这里待上一段时间吗?
Could I stay with you,for a few days?
你个白痴
You idiot.
你告诉她了
You told her.
她告诉我了
She told me.
最近家里发生了一些烂事情
Things have been crappy,at home lately.
我发现我在那里待的时间太短了
I figured I wasn't spending,enough time there.
我发现...
I figured...
事实证明,你是对的
It turns out, you're right.
总是和性有关
It's always about sex.
她有外遇了
She's been having an affair.
要啤酒吗?
Want a beer?